Guide to the William Hewlett Papers M1995
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 3: Memberships/Boards, 1930-2001
  - National Academies' Corporation: Financial Reports, 1994 (Box 512, Folder 7)
  - National Academies' Corporation: Financial Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 512, Folder 8)
  - National Academies' Corporation: Financial Reports, 1997 (Box 512, Folder 9)
  - National Academies' Corporation: Financial Reports, 1998-2000 (Box 512, Folder 10)
  - National Academies' Corporation: Howard Vollum's Memorial Tribute, 1986-1987 (Box 512, Folder 11)
    Contains correspondence and a copy of a tribute to Howard Vollum written by William Hewlett for publication by the National Academey of Engineering. Vollum was the co-founder of Tektronix, one of Hewlett-Packard's main competitors in the test and measurements field.
  - National Academies' Corporation: Publications, 1986-1987 (Box 512, Folder 12)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Annual Meeting Business Section, 1987-1997 (Box 513, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Articles of Organization and By-Laws, 1964-1998 (Box 513, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 1 of 8), 1966 (Box 513, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 2 of 8), 1966 (Box 513, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 3 of 8), 1966 (Box 513, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 4 of 8), 1966 (Box 513, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 5 of 8), 1966 (Box 513, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 6 of 8), 1966 (Box 514, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 7 of 8), 1966 (Box 514, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Committee on Membership (part 8 of 8), 1966 (Box 514, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1965-1966 (Box 514, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1965-1966 (Box 514, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1965-1966 (Box 514, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 515, Folder 1)
    Includes correspondence, schedules, and lists of members and candidates. There is one letter from Frederick Terman.
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 515, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 515, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box 515, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box 515, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 515, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 516, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1971 (Box 516, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 516, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 516, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 516, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 516, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1985-1986 (Box 516, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 516, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1987-1990 (Box 517, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1989-2001 (Box 517, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 517, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 517, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 517, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1995 (Box 517, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1996 (Box 517, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1996 (Box 517, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1996 (Box 518, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 518, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 518, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 518, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Correspondence, 1998-2001 (Box 518, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1985 (Box 519, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1986 (Box 519, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1987 (Box 519, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1988 (Box 519, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1989 (Box 519, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1990 (Box 519, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1991 (Box 520, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1992 (Box 520, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1993 (Box 520, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1994 (Box 520, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1995 (Box 521, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1996 (Box 521, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1997 (Box 521, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1998 (Box 521, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 1999 (Box 521, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Directory of Member and Foreign Associates, 2000 (Box 522, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Expense Accounts, 1966 (Box 522, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Howard Vollum Memorial Tribute, 1986-1990 (Box 522, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Memorial Tributes, Volume 3, 1989 (Box 522, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Engineering: New Member Congratulations, 1986-1989 (Box 522, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Engineering: New Member Yearbook, 1986-1988 (Box 522, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Engineering: New Member Yearbook, 1990-1992 (Box 522, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Program Report, 1986-1991 (Box 522, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Program Report, 1992-1997 (Box 523, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Engineering: Publications, 1985-2001 (Box 523, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Academy Complex Buildings Proposal, 1991 (Box 523, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Annual Report, 1985-1986 (Box 523, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 523, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 523, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Annual Report, 1994 (Box 523, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Annual Symposium on Frontiers of Science, 1991 (Box 523, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Annual Symposium on Frontiers of Science, 1993 (Box 524, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Biographical Memoirs Volume 55, 1985 (Box 524, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Biographical Memoirs Volume 56, 1987 (Box 524, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Biographical Memoirs Volume 57, 1987 (Box 525, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Biographical Memoirs Volume 58, 1989 (Box 525, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Constitution and By-Laws, 1985-1996 (Box 525, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 525, Folder 4)
    Includes correspondence, ballots, election results, meeting minutes, reports, programs, and newsletters.
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 526, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1986 (Box 526, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 526, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 526, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 526, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 526, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 526, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 527, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1993 (Box 527, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1993 (Box 527, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 527, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1994-1996 (Box 527, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1994-1996 (Box 527, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1994-1996 (Box 527, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1996 (Box 528, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1996 (Box 528, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1996 (Box 528, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 528, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1996-1997 (Box 528, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box 528, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1997-1999 (Box 529, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 529, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1999-2001 (Box 529, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Edward Ginzton, Head of Committee on Motor Vehicle Emissions, 1972 (Box 529, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Election of Member Preference Ballot, 1993 (Box 529, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Election of Member Preference Ballot, 1994 (Box 529, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Endowment, 1990-1991 (Box 529, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Expense Accounts, 1982-1983 (Box 529, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences: History, 1987-1994 (Box 529, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Meeting Itinerary, 1974 (Box 530, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1985 (Box 530, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1986 (Box 530, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1987 (Box 530, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1988 (Box 530, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1989 (Box 530, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1992 (Box 530, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1993 (Box 530, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Members' Directory, 1994 (Box 531, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Membership Directory, 1993 (Box 531, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Membership Directory, 1995 (Box 531, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Membership Directory, 1996 (Box 531, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Membership Directory, 1997 (Box 531, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Membership Directory, 1999 (Box 531, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Membership Directory, 2000 (Box 532, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: National Science Education Standards, 1994 (Box 532, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Newsletters (part 1 of 2), 1986-1998 (Box 532, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Newsletters (part 2 of 2), 1986-1998 (Box 532, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1983 (Box 532, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1985 (Box 533, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1986 (Box 533, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1987 (Box 533, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1988 (Box 533, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1989 (Box 534, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1991 (Box 534, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1992 (Box 534, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1993 (Box 534, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Organizations and Members, 1995 (Box 535, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 1 of 2), 1989 (Box 535, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 2 of 2), 1989 (Box 535, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1989-1990 (Box 535, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1990-1991 (Box 535, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 1 of 3), 1991 (Box 535, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 2 of 3), 1991 (Box 535, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 3 of 3), 1991 (Box 536, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 1 of 3), 1992 (Box 536, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 2 of 3), 1992 (Box 536, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 3 of 3), 1992 (Box 536, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1992-1993 (Box 536, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1993 (Box 536, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 1 of 3), 1994 (Box 537, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 2 of 3), 1994 (Box 537, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle (part 3 of 3), 1994 (Box 537, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1995 (Box 537, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1996 (Box 537, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1997 (Box 537, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Circle, 1997-1998 (Box 537, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: President's Message, 1984 (Box 538, Folder 1)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Publications, 1983, 1992-1993 (Box 538, Folder 2)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Report of the Treasurer, 1982-1983 (Box 538, Folder 3)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Report of the Treasurer, 1983-1985 (Box 538, Folder 4)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Report of the Treasurer, 1986-1989 (Box 538, Folder 5)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Report of the Treasurer, 1989-1991 (Box 538, Folder 6)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Report of the Treasurer, 1993-1994 (Box 538, Folder 7)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Resignation of Frank Press, 1993 (Box 538, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences: Resource Committee, 1982-1983 (Box 538, Folder 9)
  - Northern California Golf Association: Membership Cards, 1996-1998 (Box 538, Folder 10)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Correspondence, 1984-1988 (Box 538, Folder 11)
    Contains correspondence, election committee notices, financial statements, notes, and annual reports.
  - Pacific-Union Club: Correspondence, 1989-1993 (Box 538, Folder 12)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 538, Folder 13)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 539, Folder 1)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Dues and Employee Christmas Fund, 1970-1985 (Box 539, Folder 2)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Paul Reimer Membership Application, 1985-1987 (Box 539, Folder 3)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Redbook: Constitution and By-Laws and List of Present and Deceased Members, 1975-1981 (Box 539, Folder 4)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Redbook: Constitution and By-Laws and List of Present and Deceased Members, 1983-1991 (Box 539, Folder 5)
  - Pacific-Union Club: Redbook: Constitution and By-Laws and List of Present and Deceased Members, 1993-1999 (Box 539, Folder 6)
  - Palo Alto Club: Correspondence, 1994-1999 (Box 539, Folder 7)
  - Palo Alto Club: Dues and Donations, 1970-1983 (Box 539, Folder 8)
  - Palo Alto Club: Membership Roster, 1985-2000 (Box 540, Folder 1)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Academic Science Panel, 1967-1969 (Box 540, Folder 2)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Academic Science Report (part 1 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 540, Folder 3)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Academic Science Report (part 2 of 2), 1967-1968 (Box 540, Folder 4)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Appointment to Committee, 1966 (Box 541, Folder 1)
    Includes correspondence and a clipping of a news article. One letter is from President Lyndon Johnson.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Atomic Energy, 1966 (Box 541, Folder 2)
    Contains papers on Controlled Thermonuclear Research.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Atomic Energy, 1968 (Box 541, Folder 3)
    Contains papers on High Energy Physics from the Atomic Energy Commission.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Computers in Higher Education Report, 1996 (Box 541, Folder 4)
    Includes a copy of a report from 1968. Also contains information about President Clinton's Committee of Advisors on Science and Technology.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Conference on Transatlantic Technological Imbalance and Collaboration (part 1 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 541, Folder 5)
    Contains conference papers, reports, correspondence, itineraries, list of participants, summaries, and other material. The conference was held on May 25-28, 1967 in Deauville, France. Covers the perceived Technological Gap that existed between Western Europe and the United States.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Conference on Transatlantic Technological Imbalance and Collaboration (part 2 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 541, Folder 6)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Conference on Transatlantic Technological Imbalance and Collaboration (part 3 of 3), 1967-1968 (Box 541, Folder 7)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Expense Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 541, Folder 8)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: International Technical Cooperation and Assistance Panel, 1967-1968 (Box 542, Folder 1)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: List of Members, Panels and Consultants, 1968-1969 (Box 542, Folder 2)
    Contains lists of members and panels, a press release, and a letter of thanks from President Richard Nixon.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: National Academy of Education: Report on Disciplined Inquiry for Education (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box 542, Folder 3)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: National Academy of Education: Report on Disciplined Inquiry for Education (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box 542, Folder 4)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: National Institute of Education: Preliminary Plan for the Proposed Institute, 1971 (Box 542, Folder 5)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: National Research Council: Study of Postdoctoral Education in the United States, 1968 (Box 542, Folder 6)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: New England School Development Council: Teacher Competence, 1971 (Box 542, Folder 7)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Nominating Committee, 1965-1968 (Box 542, Folder 8)
    Contains correspondence, memoranda, member lists, and biographies. Includes letters from Frederick Terman, Michael Ference, David Beckler, Melvin Calvin, and Herbert York.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Panel on Educational Research and Development, 1967-1968 (Box 543, Folder 1)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Panel on Educational Research and Development, 1968-1969 (Box 543, Folder 2)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Panel on United States Government Laboratories, 1966 (Box 543, Folder 3)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Panel on Urban Problems, 1968 (Box 543, Folder 4)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Report of the Panel on the World Food Supply (part 1 of 3), 1967, 1974 (Box 543, Folder 5)
    Contains 3 volumes of the report from 1967 and a note from Charlie Anderson who sent it to Hewlett.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Report of the Panel on the World Food Supply (part 2 of 3), 1967, 1974 (Box 543, Folder 6)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Report of the Panel on the World Food Supply (part 3 of 3), 1967, 1974 (Box 544, Folder 1)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Reports on Information Systems, 1967 (Box 544, Folder 2)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Research and Education Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 544, Folder 3)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Space Science and Technology Panel, 1966-1968 (Box 544, Folder 4)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Space Science and Technology Panel, 1968-1969 (Box 544, Folder 5)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Status Reports, 1966 (Box 544, Folder 6)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Status Reports, 1967 (Box 544, Folder 7)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Status Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 544, Folder 8)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Steering Committee on International Affairs (part 1 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 545, Folder 1)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Steering Committee on International Affairs (part 2 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 545, Folder 2)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Steering Committee on International Affairs (part 3 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 545, Folder 3)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Steering Committee on International Affairs (part 4 of 4), 1967-1968 (Box 545, Folder 4)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Task Force Report, 1968-1972 (Box 545, Folder 5)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Technological Gap (part 1 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 545, Folder 6)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Technological Gap (part 2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 545, Folder 7)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Technological Gap, 1968 (Box 545, Folder 8)
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Technological Gap: Europe Trip (part 1 of 2), 1967 (Box 546, Folder 1)
    Contains notes, correspondence, guest lists, itineraries, reports, papers, and programs related to Hewlett's trip to Europe.
  - President's Science Advisory Committee: Technological Gap: Europe Trip (part 2 of 2), 1967 (Box 546, Folder 2)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Advisory Council Meeting, 1996 (Box 546, Folder 3)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Annual Report, 1995 (Box 546, Folder 4)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Board Meetings (part 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 546, Folder 5)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Board Meetings (part 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 546, Folder 6)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Board Meetings (part 1 of 3), 1995 (Box 546, Folder 7)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Board Meetings (part 2 of 3), 1995 (Box 546, Folder 8)
  - Public Policy Institute of California: Board Meetings (part 3 of 3), 1995 (Box 547, Folder 1)